{
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Find the names of all AGIs developed by 'Moritz'.",
            "expected_answer": "AGI Alpha, AGI Gamma",
            "hint": "You need to find the developer ID from the passkey table using the dev_name 'Moritz' and then use that ID to find the AGIs from the agi table."
        },
        {
            "question": "Identify the server regions where AGIs developed by 'Rohan' are located.",
            "expected_answer": "Europe",
            "hint": "Find the developer ID from the passkey table using the dev_name 'Rohan' and then use that ID to find the server regions from the server table."
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the name of the AGI with the highest compute power.",
            "expected_answer": "AGI Zeta",
            "hint": "Use the specs table to identify the AGI id with the highest compute power. Then use the agi table to find the name of the AGI."
        },
        {
            "question": "List the names of AGI that is hosted in 'Asia' and has compute power over 160.",
            "expected_answer": "AGI Iota",
            "hint": "Use the server table to find the network IDs hosted in 'Asia' and then find the corresponding AGIs from the agi table."
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the AGI with the lowest efficiency.",
            "expected_answer": "AGI Delta",
            "hint": "Use the specs table to identify the AGI with the highest efficiency. Then use the agi table to find the name of the AGI."
        },
        {
            "question": "Determine the server cost for hosting 'AGI Delta'.",
            "expected_answer": "1200",
            "hint": "Use the agi table to find the AGI ID for 'AGI Delta' and then use that ID to find the server cost from the server table."
        },
        {
            "question": "Identify the developers who have created AGIs hosted in 'Australia'.",
            "expected_answer": "Umberto",
            "hint": "Use the server table to find the network IDs hosted in 'Australia' and then use those IDs to find the developer name from the passkey table."
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the Name of the AGI with the lowest speed.",
            "expected_answer": "AGI Beta",
            "hint": "Use the specs table to identify the AGI ID with the lowest speed. Then use agi table to find the name of the AGI."
        },
        {
            "question": "Who created the first AGI in the database?",
            "expected_answer": "Jose",
            "hint": "Use the agi table to find the AGIs with the most years of operation. Then use the passkey table to find the developer name."
        },
        {
            "question": "Name the encryption method used by Joel.",
            "expected_answer": "Caesar Cipher",
            "hint": "Use the agi table to find the AGI ID for 'AGI Alpha' and then use that ID to find the encryption key from the passkey table."
        },
        {
            "question": "Name the encryption method used by Claudio.",
            "expected_answer": "ROT13 Cipher",
            "hint": "Use the agi table to find the AGI ID for 'AGI Alpha' and then use that ID to find the encryption key from the passkey table."
        }

    ]
}
